{
    "id": "1d002969ed854b5b9804174c6a31a7c8",
    "title": "Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She congratulated …………………………..",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, use the reflexive pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "herself",
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are worse than …………………………….",
            "description": "Object pronouns are considered more appropriate after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "himself",
                "he",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He stabbed ………………………….. with a knife.",
            "description": "When the subject and the object refer to the same person, use the reflexive pronoun. ",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "himself",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Whose car is this?’ ‘It is …………………………..’",
            "description": "It is hers means the same as it is her car. ",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He lives on ………………………….. own.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "himself",
                "him"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I did it …………………………… as there was no one to help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "myselves",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Please eat more vegetables and do …………………………. a favor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "yourself",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is your fault, not ………………………….",
            "description": "Not mine means the same as not my fault. ",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "mine",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I showed her my ID proof, but she couldn’t show me ………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "That cat of ………………………….. has drank my milk.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours",
                "yourself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………….. spoke to the Minister.",
            "description": "For emphasis, use the emphatic pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "myself",
                "me",
                "myselves"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This cat is …………………………..",
            "description": "That cat is theirs means the same as that is their cat. ",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}